Arun Kumar M

Lead Generation / Business Development Professional

Gerugambakkam Chennai, TN 600122

T+91 904 364 8175



arunk6252@gmail.com



EXPERIENCE

July 2017 -Present

INDIUM SOFTWARE INC

Senior Executive, Business Development

- Generate New Revenue with new leads
- Scheduling Calls and F2F Meetings
- Documentations Works (i.e. NDA, SOW, WO, MSA)
- Create and submit RFIs, RFPs and Presentations
- Collaborate in Community to understand and build rapport with Gaming Professional (i.e. Discord, Facebook, twitter, Steam etc.,)
- SPOC between Client and Delivery Team
- Co-ordinate with Finance team regarding the invoices/ Payments

Accomplishments:

- Brave Heart of Indium Q1 2018
- Creative Thinker Q2 2018

May 2016 -July 2017

KARYA TECHNOLOGIES INC

Executive – Business Development

- Market research, Lead Generation
- Run Email Campaign's
- Schedule Calls with CXO's, VP and Directors

Accomplishments:

Star (Best) Performer of the month - September,
 November 2016, January, February and March 2017

ABOUT ME

Experienced Salesperson with a proven record of achieving the target along with very good communicational and Lead Generation skills. Also has vast knowledge on various industries including Computer Games, Entertainment, ISV's, Hospitals & Healthcare, Banking, Retail, Insurance etc.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Lead Generation * * * * *

Market Research * * * *

Business Develop. * * * *

Cold Calling * * *

Team Handling * * *

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication * * * * * *

Tech Competency * * * * *

Work Ethics * * * *

Flexible * * * *

Leadership * * *

EDUCATION

2019-2021 M.SC CYBER FORENSIC & INFORMATION SECURITY

UNIVERSITY OF MADRAS

2013-2016 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

A.M JAIN COLLEGE

REFERENCES

Pawan Choubey T +91 988 456 8543

pawanchoubey970@gmail.com

Ivaraj Nesan T +91 938 427 7469 Ivaraj.s@indiumsoft.com